Guide to the Catholic Apostolic Church Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Sermons and Treatises, 1825-1971, n.d.; Series I
  - Heath, Edward (1845-1929) (see also: Ashford, E)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - The Deacons' Position as the Assistant to the Celebrant at the Holy Eucharist, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Sermon, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Two Homilies Delivered at Albury, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Notes on Spiritual Healing, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Two Homilies Delivered at Albury, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - From A Sermon on "The Chapel of the Great King", 1929 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Cremation, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Homily, n.d (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - The Ministry of the Word for Cleansing, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Heath, Herbert (1849-1936)
    - The Divine Victim, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Sermon: The Ministry of Archangels, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Sermon Preached at the church in Bishopgate, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Church in Bristol, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Church in Bristol: Sermon by the Angel in Charge, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Sermon, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Heath, James. B (1834-1915)
    - The Locusts as a Fourfold Historical Type, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Heath, James Shaft (1875-1961)
    - Ten Discourses on the Book of Revelation: Delivered in the Church of Glasgow, 1931-1932 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Heath, Rupert Maunsell (1881- )
    - Teaching on the History and meaning of the Monthly Assembly of the Seven Churches in London, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Vestments as ordered by the Apostles: A Lecture, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Lecture on the Ceremonial and Symbolism of the Service for the Assembly of the Seven Churches in London, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - A Lecture on the full Services of morning and evening Prayer and their relation to the worship of the Tabernacle and the Temple (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Hillard, Abraham
    - Sermon on Martha and Mary, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Hooper, Edmund Lewis (1828-1888)
    - Christmas Day: A Sermon Preached in Albury, 1882 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Howell, Clarence Charles ( 1947)
    - Two Sermon on Esther, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Hughes, Richard
    - Israel's Future, 1881 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Hume, Henry Strange (1840-1928)
    - Sermons: All Saints, 1900 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Pastoral Letter on the death of Mr Woodhouse, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - An Address, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Three Sermons on Marriage, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Irving, Edward (1792-1834)
    - Immediate Events in the Church Unfolded from Prophecy: The Exposition and Sermon, 1832 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Exposition and Sermon, 1832 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Exposition and Sermon, 1832 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Exposition and Sermon, 1832 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Exposition, Sermon and Address, 1832 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Exposition and Sermon, 1832 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Exposition and Sermon, 1832 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Irving's Last Letter to his Flock and to Mr. Cardale, 1832 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Irving, Martin How
    - Sermon on Coadjutorship, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Jarvis, Alexander ( -1897)
    - Conversations on Baptism: The Mode of Baptism, 1884 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Conversations on Baptism: The Subjects of Baptism, 1885 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Jennings, Samuel ( - 1916)
    - The Great Problem; or, Man's future Place and Work in the Universe, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Ker, David ( -1883)
    - Observations on Mrs. Oliphant's "Life of Edward Irving:" and Correction of certain Misstatements therein, 1863 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - King-Church, Norman Lawrie (1874-1938)
    - Sermon, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Sermon, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Lecture on the Tabernacle, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Kretschmer, Adolf ( -1928)
    - Address on Psalm LXXX, 2,3, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Law, George (see also: Gaird, William Renny)
    - The Catholic Apostolic Church and the Rev John Andrew, Dundee, 1869 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - The Catholic Apostolic Church and the Editor of 'The Christian News' (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Leslie, John (1814-1897)
    - The Suppression of the Spirit, 1868 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Levesley, William Charles ( -1940)
    - Sermon, 1865 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - M'Clelland, George
    - Examination of the Statements in the Lectures on "The Fatherhood of God", 1865 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - McDonald, John Bay Athole (1836-1919) (see also: Ashford, E)
    - The First Chapter of Genesis: A Lecture, n.d.. (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - McMichael, A. John W.
    - Sermon; Joseph and his Brethren, 1910 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Malcolm, George ( -1897)
    - By Man Came death; By Man Came also the Resurrection of the Dead, 1888 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Maunder, Edward Walter (1851-1928)
    - Sermon, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Sermon, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Middleton, H (1871-1956?)
    - Sermon: The Threefold Method of the Lord's appearing, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Morrison, James
    - The Declaration, " I pray not for the World", 1845 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Morris, George
    - Two Discourses on the Coming of our Lord Jesus Christ, 1867 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Nash, Robert (1814-1899)
    - On Development: A Sermon Preached at Albury, 1887 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Nash, Thomas Alexander N. (1844-1934)
    - Spiritual Gifts, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Norton, Robert ( -1883)
    - Agnus Dei: The Lamb of God, 1867 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Orme, William
    - An Expostulatory Letter to the Rev. Edward Irving, 1825? (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Parker, Thomas Henry
    - The Litany: Its Origin, Growth, and Use, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - The Sermons on the Number 666, or Man's Final Systematic to Shape his own Destiny, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Sermon; Divorce, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - The Covering of the Holy Table, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Pearl, Samuel Thomas ( -1944)
    - Pastoral Instruction: The Penitential Psalms, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Peck, Jasper Kenrick (1832-1905)
    - Sermon: The Place and State of the Departed, 1880? (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Homily: Separation of the Apostles, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Perceval, Spencer (1795-1859)
    - Speech in the House of Commons... On a General Fast., 1831 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - A Word of Encouragement to Those Who Pray and Wait for the Coming of the Lord, 1856 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Pitcairn, William Fettes ( -1891)
    - The Passion and the Resurrection of the Lord: Meditations and Exhortations, 1867 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Place, William Henry (1800-1866)
    - St. George's in-the East and Italy: God's Retribution on Insubordinate Clergy and Worldly Churches, 1860 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Pochhammer, Max von (1822-1895)
    - To the Angel Evangelists, Angels of the Churches, Etc., in the Central Part of the Tribe in North Germany, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Prentice, James Filgate (1813-1881)
    - Notes on the Book of Revelation, 187? (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Incense of Rams, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Priddle, David (1853-1932)
    - Progress in Christ, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Proby, William Henry Baptist (1832-1915)
    - Letters on the Art of Christian Preaching, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Purkiss, W
    - Some Thoughts on the Spiritual Symbolism of Music, 1884
  - Rawson, Thomas Edward (1859-1943)
    - Sermon to the Flock: The Deluge and the Ark, 1902 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Two Sermons on Daniel VIII, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Sermon: The Cities of Refuge, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Substance of a Sermon, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Teaching on the Removal of the Last Apostle and the Last Coadjutor, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Church in Southwark: Teaching, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Armageddon, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Remarks on Sponsorship in Holy Baptism, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Rutter, Charles J.
    - Cremation versus Christian Burial: A Word of Warning in Two Parts, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Schrey, Karl (1870-1960)
    - Sermon by the Late Angel of Siegen, Germany, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Schwartz
    - The Chronicle of the Setting Up Of The Church in Berlin, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Sinclair, Rev. Sutherland
    - The Bottle, and Those Who Tempt their neighbors to the sinful Use of It, 1859 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Sitwell, Francis
    - Letter Written by Mr.Francis Sitwell to His Sister, Mary, 1834? (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - The Covenant of Baptism, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Stewart, Hugh (1833-1912)
    - Sermon: The Ministry of Archangels, 1907 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Symes, Langford Rowley (1801-1875)
    - The Recent Decree on the Immaculate Conception of the Blessed Virgin Mary: A Sign of the Present Time: A Sermon, 1854 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - An Address on the Coming of the Lord, and the Preparation of the Church, 1866 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Taplin, Edward Oliver (1800-1862)
    - Nine Lectures on 'Spiritual Gifts', 1833 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Ministry on Numbers, 1849 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Six Ministries... on the Condition of the Departed, 1850 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - The Study of the Holy Scriptures, 1851 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - The Signs of the Coming of the Lord, 1, 1851 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - The Signs of the Coming of the Lord, 2, 1851 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - The Signs of the Coming of the Lord, 3, 1851 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - The Signs of the Coming of the Lord, 4, 1851 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - The Signs of the Coming of the Lord, 5, 1851 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - The Signs of the Coming of the Lord, 6, 1851 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - The Signs of the Coming of the Lord, 7, 1851 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - The Signs of the Coming of the Lord, 8, 1851 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - The Signs of the Coming of the Lord, 9, 1851 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - The Signs of the Coming of the Lord, 10, 1851 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Cycles and the Ten Virgins, 1854 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Gog and Magog, 1855 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - The Patriarch Shem and his Generations as a Type of the Workings of God in the Church of Christ, 1861 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Teaching on the Book of Esther, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Teaching on the Number 40..., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Teaching on the Prophecies of Jacob...and Those of Moses (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Tarbet, William ( -1881)
    - Third Discourse on infant Baptism, 1850 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - The Signs of the Last Days: Part First, 1853 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - The Signs of the Last Days: Part Second, 1853 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Spiritual Manifestations in the Present Day, 1855 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Astronomy and Geology as taught in the Holy Scriptures, 1855 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - The Shadows of the Law: The Realities of the Body of Christ; Part 1, 1892? (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - The Shadows of the Law: The Realities of the Body of Christ; Part 11, 1892? (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - The Shadows of the Law: The Realities of the Body of Christ; Part 111, 1892? (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - The Shadows of the Law: The Realities of the Body of Christ; Part IV, 1892? (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - The Shadows of the Law: The Realities of the Body of Christ; Part V, 1892? (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Thiersch, Heinrich Wilhelm Josias ( 1817-1885)
    - On Private Confession and Absolution, 1900 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - A Sermon Delivered at the Apostles' Chapel at Albury, 1901 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Pastoral Teaching, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Pastoral Teaching, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Pastoral Teaching, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Thonger, James (1839-1861)
    - Eight Sermons on the :The Seventy", 1887 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Teaching to the Flock, 1896 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Teaching by the Angel to the Flock, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Tudor, John Owen (1783-1861)
    - Sunday the Creation Sabbath, 1850 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Six Lectures on the Apocalypse, 1861 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Valentin, Anton (1865-1951)
    - The Gospel in the Book of Exodus, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - The Sacrament of the Eucharist and Its Solemn Removal From the Altar, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Sermon on Isaiah VI, 1-8, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Velden, George ( -1930)
    - Untitled, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Wagener, Carl Louis Wilhelm ( -1922)
    - The Double Witness: A Sermon..., 1905 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Sermon: Day of Pentecost, 1911 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Walker, Andrew ( -1888)
    - The Cake of Barley Bread: Whoso eateth Thereof Shall be blessed, 1857 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Wallis, Ferdinand
    - Letter on the Archangel Ministry, 1902 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Wells, Charles Augustus Este (1846-1923)
    - The Mystery of the Incarnation, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Sermon Preached at Albury on Good Friday, 1907 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Homily Delivered at Albury, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Willis, Algernon Merwood ( 1920)
    - On the Form and Order of the Holy Eucharist (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Winder, A
    - Music in Churches, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Witherby, George ( 1822-1909)
    - The Gospel of Genesis, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - A Sermon, 1901 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Homily, 1904 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Woodhouse, Francis ( 1805-1901)
    - The Book of Esther, 1859 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - A Teaching on the Prophetic Office, 1867 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Address on the death of Mr. Cardale, 1877 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Teaching: The Progressive Development of the Lord's Work, 1877 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Teaching delivered in the Assembly of the Seven Churches in London, 1878 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Address, 1878 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Address ...at the Meeting of the Seven Churches..., 1881 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Teaching, 1881 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Faith Healing and the Salvation Army, 1885 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Wright, William Walter (1824-1911)
    - The Exceeding Sinfulness of Sin, 1885 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - The Burden of the Desert of the Sea, 1888 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Zangger, Theodor Findlater (1864-1940)
    - Sermon to the Congregation in Albury, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Anonymous ( 1856-1912)
    - The Two Smaller Testimonies, 1885 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - The Testimony to His Majesty King William IV..., 1836 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Testimony to all who Profess the Faith of Christ..., 1858 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - The Human Body As A Symbol of the Body of Christ, 1856 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - A General Description and Explanation of Drawing of the Tabernacle, The Pattern of Which God Gave to Moses, 1865 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Pastoral Instruction: The Present Condition of the Departed, 1876 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Sermon on Romans 15.13, 1881 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - A Word of Testimony Respectfully Addressed to the Archbishop and Bishops of the Church of England, 1888 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Pastoral Teaching, 1904 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Pastoral Teaching, 1907 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Pastoral Teaching, 1908 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Sermon: Joseph, Judah and Benjamin, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Sermon on Daniel IX, 22-25, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Sermon (Easter Day), 1910 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - The Congregation in Albury: Teachings By Priests, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Sermon, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Anonymous (1913-1956)
    - The Congregation in Albury: Ministry by Priests, 1913 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Sermon, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Sermon, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Sermon, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - New Year Sermon, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - The Armistice and Peace: (The Number Eleven), 1919 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - (Sermon) Church in Birmingham, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - "Distress of Nations with Perplexity", 1930 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Sermon, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - ...Letter by the Danish Member of the Flock..., 1936 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Pastoral no 836; Sermon, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - The Council of Zion, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Anonymous (n.d.)
    - Albury Homily, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Be Not Afraid Only Believe, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Dialogue Respecting the Rule of Faith for Protestants, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Four Sermons on Freemasonry, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Keeping The Lord's Secret, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - The Lord's Controversy and the Type of Miriam (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - The Lord's Tithe, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - The Miracle of the Feeding of the Five Thousand and the four Thousand (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - The Songs of degrees, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - The Man After God's own Heart, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - To All Who Profess the Faith of Christ, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Not related to Apostolic Church
    - Campbell, Rollo
      - Two Lectures on Canada, 1857 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Grant, Rev. Brewin
      - Report of a Public Discussion Between Grant and George J. Holyoake,Esq., 1854 (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - Discussion Between Rev. Grant and Mr Holyoake, 1854 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Holyoake, G. Jacob
      - The Logic of Death, or Why Should the Atheist Fear to die, 1853 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Mahan, Asa
      - The Relation of Christianity to the Freedom of Human Thought and Action, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Rutherford, J.H
      - Challenges; A Narrative and Appeal, 1854 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Shaw, Col.I.A
      - A Stray Leaf, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Stevenson, John
      - A Soul Strengthening and Comforting Cordial, 1847 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Tregelles, S.P.
      - The Man of Sin, 1850 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Anonymous
      - The Pre- Millennian Advent of the Savior, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - Limitarian Jesuitry Exposed, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - The Logic of Holyake's 'Logic Of Death', 1854 (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - The Model of A Moorish Lady, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - Present Dispensation- Its Course, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - The Tariff of Conscience, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Historical Lists and Descriptions, 1826-1973, n.d.; Series II
  - Annals: The Lord's Work in the Nineteenth and Twentieth Centuries, 1889-1963 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Annals: "Apostles and Other Ministers"; Notes on the History of the Church" (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Bibliography: Bibliography of Catholic Apostolic Church Printed Publications, 1908 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Bibliography: Lists of CAC publications, c.1973 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Biography: "Biographical Index of those Associated with the Lord's Work", compiled by Seraphim Newman-Norton (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - "The Lord's Restored Apostles", n.d. (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - "The Albury Meetings, November, 1826" (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - "Kirchliches Addressbuch 1928" (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Information regarding Church Buildings, 1851-1937,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Tools For Worship And Instruction, 1885-1973, n.d.; Series III
  - Liturgy: Charts and Lectonaries, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Liturgy: Orders of Worship, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Materials relating to doctrinal instruction and polity (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Report of the First Meeting of the Class of Young People, 1906 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Analytical Arrangement of the Book of Revelation, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Table of the Council of Zion, 1885 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Some of God's Ordinances or Channels of Blessings, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 72)